<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>PI Company on Documentation for Hugo Learn Theme</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content in PI Company on Documentation for Hugo Learn Theme</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2018 19:22:05 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Credits</title>
      <link>/credits/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2018 19:22:05 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/credits/</guid>
      <description>Credits:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Letsencrypt Acme Nginx</title>
      <link>/tutorial/linux/letsencrypt-acme-nginx/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Jan 2018 19:08:01 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/tutorial/linux/letsencrypt-acme-nginx/</guid>
      <description>Introduction This is a guide how to set up your free SSL certificate for your web-server with Letsencrypt&amp;rsquo;s acme client on an Ubuntu linux server.
Installation First of all we have to install the NGINX web server
sudo apt install nginx  Next step is to install the certbot via the certbot&amp;rsquo;s lauchpad repository
sudo apt-get install software-properties-common sudo add-apt-repository ppa:certbot/certbot sudo apt-get update sudo apt-get install certbot python-certbot-nginx  We have all dependency installed so lets configure it!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Postfix DKIM</title>
      <link>/tutorial/linux/postfix-opendkim/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Jan 2018 19:07:41 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/tutorial/linux/postfix-opendkim/</guid>
      <description>Introduction The frustration of getting falsely flagged as a spammer is not strange to most of the mail server admins. By excluding the possibility of a compromised server, a false flag is usually caused by one of the following:
 the server is an open mail relay the sender&amp;rsquo;s or server&amp;rsquo;s IP address is blacklisted the server does not have a FQDN and a PTR record the Sender Policy Framework (SPF) DNS record is missing or it is misconfigured the DomainKeys Identified Mail (DKIM) implementation is missing or it&amp;rsquo;s not properly set up These are some of the basic properties that are being checked by the majority of proprietary and open source spam filters (including SpamAssassin).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Domain Name System (DNS)</title>
      <link>/wiki/domain-name-system/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/wiki/domain-name-system/</guid>
      <description>The domain name system (DNS) is the way that internet domain names are located and translated into internet protocol (IP) addresses. The domain name system maps the name people use to locate a website to the IP address that a computer uses to locate a website. For example, if someone types www.google.com into a web browser, a server behind the scenes will map that name to the IP address 216.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Open Mail Relay</title>
      <link>/wiki/open-mail-relay/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/wiki/open-mail-relay/</guid>
      <description>An open mail relay is an SMTP server configured in such a way that it allows anyone on the Internet to send e-mail through it, not just mail destined to or originating from known users. This used to be the default configuration in many mail servers; indeed, it was the way the Internet was initially set up, but open mail relays have become unpopular because of their exploitation by spammers and worms.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>